新的一天開始
The day begins
她打理好自己的容貌
She makes herself look pure
我知道她會轉頭的
I know she'll turn some heads
我敢跟你保證
of that I'm sure
你看看她，如此華麗
Now you know she's looking fine
如此崇高，如此神聖
All so divine, all so sublime
她還要工作
She gets to work
你不知道針要趕快補？
Don't you know a stitch in time saves nine?
當大家看到她走過來
When they all see her come around,
就知道有什麼特別的
you know there's something here to be found
心中湧出美麗
the lush beauty
如同鑽戒一般
like a diamond ring
它是如此的珍奇
of the highest Rarity
它的美麗不只這樣
And even more beautiful inside,
再深入點你就知道
reach way down deep and I'm sure you'll find
她能給你
that she can bring
那顆所謂的
that little something
慷慨的心
called Generosity
如此優雅，她跳著華爾滋穿過人群
So elegant, as she waltzes across the room
看她閃耀
Watch her shine now
視線都在她身上
Her time, it will come soon
我們不要管這麼多了
Now let's use just what we know
來吧，我們一起跳隻舞
C'mon now let's go, go, go
我們別管時間了
And dance the night away
就一起跳到最後一刻
until we all have to go home
當大家看到她走過來
When they all see her come around,
就知道有什麼特別的
you know there's something here to be found
心中湧出美麗
the lush beauty
如同鑽戒一般
like a diamond ring
它是如此的珍奇
of the highest Rarity
它的美麗不只這樣
And even more beautiful inside,
再深入點你就知道
reach way down deep and I'm sure you'll find
她能給你
that she can bring
那顆所謂的
that little something
慷慨的心
called Generosity
來看月光照耀那雙水藍的眼睛
Now come watch the moonlight reflect off her sapphire eyes
我要跟你在一起到永遠－
I'll stick by you forever and every single day-
－我們的關係只會越來越親密
-to forge and reinforce the bonds that tie us
大家一起完成這和聲
Now come and join me in harmony
這是我人生最美好的事情
This is the best possible thing
她會在這等著你們
She'll be here waiting
一起大聲唱出來
for you all to break out and sing
隨著我漸漸睡著
And late at night, I wonder
我好奇著一些事情
as I lay my head down to slumber
我把時間編在一起
I weave through time
(她把時間編在一起)
(She weaves through time)
好像一件華麗的洋裝般
like a dress in design, it's true
我要對你展現我的慷慨心
Just know I could be generous to you
(希望我能對你展現慷慨心)
(I wish I could be generous to you)
(展現慷慨心)
(Generous to you)
當我看到她走過來
When I see her come around
(當你看到我走過來)
(When you see me come around)
就知道有什麼特別的
I know there's something there to be found
心中湧出美麗
the lush beauty
如同鑽戒一般
like a diamond ring
它是如此的珍奇
of the highest Rarity
它的美麗不只這樣
And even more beautiful inside,
再深入點幫我找找
reach way down deep and help me find
我能給你
I can bring
那顆所謂的
that little something
慷慨的心
called Generosity